Tom Shaffir

Cell: 0533320792 Email: tom6016@gmail.com

> YoB: 1987 Residence: Tel Aviv

Strong analytical abilities, questioning mind and critical thinking; fast learner - quickly fits in; team player with excellent interpersonal skills. Highly motivated, experience in managing people.

- A year and a half experience in programming and developing on C language, platform Linux.
- Verifiction script writing on Python language.
- Worked with Git, Linux/Unix & MARS (mellanox tools) on daily basis.

Education

2012-2016 B.sc. in computer science; Tel Hai College. (graduation score:85). Psychometric score: 720.
2003-2006 Full matriculation; Math, Physics, English (5 Units), emek High School (score: 106)

Professional Experience

2015-2016 MELLANOX TECHNOLOGIES, Linux Drivers developer

Mellanox Technologies is an Israeli supplier of end-to-end InfiniBand and Ethernet interconnect solutions and services for servers and storage.

- A student job assigned to R&D team, the team goal is developing & supporting complex data traffic abilitis (Ethernet, Infiniband).
- Drivers code writing (Infiniband) on both C & Assembly language.
- Code testing via Python scripts writing.
- Failures Monitoring & repairing on redmine platform and Git for shared code work.
- Using Scrum work method as a company standard.

•

2014-2015 Biotechnology Preparatory, tel-hai college, teacher assistant

The College promotes and emphasizes the advancement of science, society and the environment in Israel. All while adopting an open and advanced teaching methods and combination of high quality speakers.

- Student teaching towards a final math exam, level of math equels to differential and integral course.
- Frontal teaching both groups & individuals. Especially practical teaching.

2013-2014 teacher assistant, Danziger High School

- Students Tuter towards various final exams in math, English.
- Class counts up to 15 students.

Military Service

2006-2011 RANK: officer captain (3 stripes) unit 76. Full mandatory service as a fighter on golani special elit force, Permanent service as intelligence officer in unit 76 (intelligence wing). Up to 25 soldiers were under my command.

Software & practical knowledge

Highly familiar with the following communications protocols: Unicast, Multicast, TCP/IP, OSPF, STP, IGMP, VRRP

languages